<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John Grace Suits</title>
    <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/</link>
    <description>Recent content on John Grace Suits</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Wear A Tuxedo</title>
      <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/blog/2018/05/17/weartux/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/blog/2018/05/17/weartux/</guid>
      <description>Style Guide
  A tuxedo is a classic no matter what, if you’re off to a posh do then you need to know how to wear one, and it’s not as tricky as you’d think.
Now it’s unlikely that your work requires you to wear a tux everyday (unless you’re 007), but there comes a time in a man’s life when he has to go somewhere really fancy. When that happens a tuxedo is really the only clothing option, and as long as you know exactly how to pull one off, it’s not that much of a pain to wear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Traditional Values With A Modern Attitude</title>
      <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/blog/2016/08/29/traditionalvalues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/blog/2016/08/29/traditionalvalues/</guid>
      <description>Chivalry is not dead &amp;hellip; proof today’s guys can be perfect gents A MODERN gentleman still displays the good manners of his forebears, according to a study.
He is as respectful, polite and kind as any chivalrous knight of old, as he holds the door open for others, pays attention when people speak and always keeps his shoes nice and shiny.
The 21st-century code of etiquette also includes putting his mobile phone away at the dinner table, keeping fit and wearing a good suit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More Than Ever, It&#39;s About Fit</title>
      <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/blog/2012/04/11/aboutfit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/blog/2012/04/11/aboutfit/</guid>
      <description>Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter what kind of suit you&amp;rsquo;re investing in, whether it&amp;rsquo;s $200 or $2,000, flannel or seersucker, two-button or three. We&amp;rsquo;ve seen plenty of guys who&amp;rsquo;ve bought the right suit and let it hang off them like an NBA rookie on draft night. And we&amp;rsquo;ve seen men in cheap but well-tailored suits who look like a million bucks. The thing&amp;rsquo;s got to fit right, or else there&amp;rsquo;s no point in wearing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/test/</guid>
      <description>testing</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are ready to help you We at John Grace Suits are available every day to help you get your own John Grace suit. Please fill out the following form and we will get back to you shortly about setting up an appointment.

If there are any issues with your order, please feel free to contact us using the same form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>F1 Driver&#39;s Show</title>
      <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/f1/</guid>
      <description>With the help of International F1 Drivers Marc Gene, Antonio Giovinazzi, Sean Gelael, Sergey Sirotkin &amp;amp; Norman Nato, John Grace took to the runway at Singapore F1 showcasing our 2018 collection of suits &amp;ldquo;Life In the Fast Lane&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/faq/</guid>
      <description>These frequently asked questions provide more information about how we make suits.

1. WHAT SHOULD I DO IF I HAVE STILL NOT RECEIVED THE ORDER? 
Make sure you have the correct tracking number. If you do, orders may simply be delayed due to customs, needing to order more fabric, or any other of a multitude of reasons. You may contact us to help you resolve this issue, but we normally send an email notification of any delays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://as4mo3.github.io/JohnGraceSuits/services/</guid>
      <description>Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante. Donec eu libero sit amet quam egestas semper. Aenean ultricies mi vitae est. Mauris placerat eleifend leo.

1. WHAT DO WE OFFER? 
Pellentesque habitant morbi tristique senectus et netus et malesuada fames ac turpis egestas. Vestibulum tortor quam, feugiat vitae, ultricies eget, tempor sit amet, ante.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>